(zipper noise) Z. (zipper noise) z. Zzz, Zzz, Zzz.
Zzz, Zebras. (piano music) Zzz.
Zzz, Zipper. Zip, Zip, Zip. (zipper noise) Zzz.
Zzz, Zoo. (elephant trumpets) (elephant trumpets) (lion yawns) Zzz.
Click and drag the puzzle pieces to make a word. (click) Zzz. (click) Ih. (click) Guh. (click) Zzz. (click) Ah. (click) Guh.
Zzz. Ih. Guh. Zzz. Ih. Guh. Zig. Zzz. Ah. Guh. Zzz. Ah. Guh. Zag. Zigzag.
(upbeat music) I am a little zigzag boy, who goes this way and that. I never know just where to put, my coat or shoes or hat.
(upbeat music) I am a little zigzag girl, who flutters here and there. I never know just where to find, my brush to fix my hair.
(upbeat music) I am a little zigzag boy who goes this way and that. I am a little zigzag girl who flutters here and there. I never know just where to put my coat or shoes or hat. I never know just where to find my brush to fix my hair. So we are little zigzag people, that's the way it goes. We never know just where to put, our brushes or our clothes. (laughing)
Zzz. Goodbye.
THE END